kingsofchaos.com 2005-02-04

# Kings of Chaos :: Massively Multiplayer Online Role Playing Game

Advertise here

|    

## PRIVACY STATEMENT

### Information Collection and Use

#### Information Collection

KingsOfChaos.com is the sole owner of the information collected on KingsOfChaos.com. KingsOfChaos.com collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site. 

#### Registration

In order to use this Web site, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give a valid email address. We use this information to verify that the user is not attempting to gain an unfair advantage by registering multiple accounts automatically in his/her name. It is optional for the user to provide information such as his/her name, country, age, and zip code. We use this information for statistical purposes only. 

### Information Use

#### Profile

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third parties to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the users personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user's visit to our Web site. We do not share your profile with other third parties. 

#### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. 

By setting a cookie on our site, users would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site, however, their ability to experience the site will be severely limited because cookies are an integral part of our site’s authentication system. Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. See the Profile section. 

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, nor can we access any data obtained from their use, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. 

#### Third Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp)

#### Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by KingsOfChaos.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

#### Log Files

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are tied to personally identifiable information to enable our Web-based service. We use an analysis utility called AWStats that uses log files to analyze traffic and user movement. 

### Communications from the Site

#### Account Activation

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username, and that the e-mail address they have provided is in fact a valid e-mail address. 

#### Service Announcements

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. We reserve the right to send an e-mail to our users if, for instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature. 

#### Customer Service

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email, in accordance with the users wishes. 

### Sharing

#### Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. 

#### Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, KingsOfChaos.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

#### Surveys

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Anonymous survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Users' personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless we give prior notice and choice. 

#### Chat Rooms, Message Boards, and Public Forums

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through e-mail, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. 

#### Security

This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line. 

#### Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users’ personally identifiable information. This can usually be done by emailing our Customer Support at privacy@kingsofchaos.com. 

#### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days. 

#### Contact Information

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please [contact us](mailto:%61%64%6d%69%6e%40%6b%69%6e%67%73%6f%66%63%68%61%6f%73%2e%63%6f%6d). 

Report Spam | Privacy Policy | Advertising | [Business Queries](mailto:%62%69%7a%64%65%76%40%6b%69%6e%67%73%6f%66%63%68%61%6f%73%2e%63%6f%6d) | Terms of Service | [Store](http://www.99dogs.com/portal/associate.html?assoc=WSN-MV4&page=store&item=16503)

Created by Rocco, Ben, Aman, and Nick  
_Copyright © 2003-2005 Kings of Chaos, All rights reserved._
